{
    "id": "d32c7f657ed647c2b70efa19c9a03789",
    "title": "Mixed Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "cc1f5808518c43f4a4cd2f5a38880eb8",
            "title": "Mixed Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Put a coat .................................. before going out.",
                    "description": "To put a coat on is to wear it.",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "in",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The business was losing money, so they closed it ............................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "off",
                        "down"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am going to the airport to see .................................... my friend.",
                    "description": "To see off is to go to the railway station or airport to say goodbye to someone who is leaving.",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "off",
                        "of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "It is always a good idea to take .................................. travel insurance.",
                    "description": "To take out travel insurance is to purchase it.",
                    "answers": [
                        "off",
                        "up",
                        "out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The doctor advised him to give ................................. smoking.",
                    "description": "To give up smoking is to quit smoking.",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "on",
                        "up",
                        "off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I make it a point to catch .................................. my sleep when I am on holiday.",
                    "description": "To catch up on sleep is to sleep for an extra hour or two.",
                    "answers": [
                        "up in",
                        "up",
                        "on",
                        "up on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                },
                {
                    "question": "Because of your irresponsible act, we got caught ................................ in a great deal of trouble.",
                    "description": "To get caught up in trouble is to land yourself in trouble.",
                    "answers": [
                        "off",
                        "up",
                        "out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "This achievement calls ................................ a celebration.",
                    "description": "If something calls for something, it necessitates it.",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "in",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Her performance was amazing. I was blown .................................... by it.",
                    "description": "When you are blown away by something, you find it to be absolutely brilliant. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "out",
                        "up",
                        "away"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She has come ...................................... a lot of criticism over the manner in which she handled the situation.",
                    "description": "to come in for criticism is to receive it.",
                    "answers": [
                        "up for",
                        "in for",
                        "on for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I came ....................................... these old photographs while I was clearing up the closets.",
                    "description": "To come across something is to find it by chance.",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "at",
                        "across"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The company chalked ..................................... record profits last year.",
                    "description": "To chalk up profits is to earn profits.",
                    "answers": [
                        "out",
                        "up",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}